Philip Amwata

Full Stack Software Developer





PROFFESINOAL SUMMARY

Full-Stack Software Developer interested in using innovative technological solutions to address socioeconomic challenges. Worked on web and mobile applications involving technologies such as C#, ASP.NET, .NET, Angular, NodeJs, NestJs, AWS, GCP, Terraform, Docker, RabbitMQ and Firebase

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, Specno - Software and Design Agency

Jan. 2021 – Present Full-Stack Software Development

- Developing views using Angular, Typescript, HTML5
- Data manipulation, state management, service development and storage using RxJs, NGRX, Nodejs with Nestjs, Firebase, RabbitMQ, MS SQL Server, Postgres and C#.NET
- Cloud Solutions using AWS and GCP with Docker, Terraform
- Managing projects and development teams as the Lead Developer
- Creating and reviewing requirements, code and software systems
- Conducting Technical Assessments and Technical Interview

Software Developer, Dipar Systems

Oct. 2019 – Jan. 2021 Full-Stack Software Development

- Developing views using AngularJS and jQuery
- Data manipulation using C# .NET and MSSQL
- Handling support tickets and change requests

Python tutor, university of Cape Town

Mar. 2019-Oct. 2019

- Tutor students on programming fundamentals using the Python programming language
- · Assess student progress during weekly lab sessions
- Mark students' practical and theoretical work

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF Cape Town, cape town, western cape

Mar. 2017 - Dec. 2020

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and Computer Games Development